let array = [
    {
        "question": "How many Major Languages?",
        "answer": "3 - Hausa, Igbo, Yoruba",
        "color": "bg-red-500"
    },

    {
        "question": "Capital of the country?",
        "answer": "Abuja, FCT",
        "color": "bg-gray-500"
    },

    {
        "question": "Weather patterns",
        "answer": "2 distinct seasons, rainy and Dry season",
        "color": "bg-green-500"
    },

    {
        "question": "Current president",
        "answer": "Muhammadu Buhari",
        "color": "bg-lime-500"
    },

    {
        "question": "Richest Man",
        "answer": "Aliko Dangote",
        "color": "bg-teal-500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Popular Foods",
        "answer": "Jollof Rice, Amala, Fufu",
        "color": "bg-sky-500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Closet Neighbors",
        "answer": "Ghana, Cotonou",
        "color": "bg-yellow-500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Most popular sport",
        "answer": "Football(Soccer)",
        "color": "bg-purple-500"
    },    
    {
        "question": "Currency",
        "answer": "Naira",
        "color": "bg-blue-500"
    },    
    {
        "question": "Most spoken Language",
        "answer": "Pidgin(A varied form of english)",
        "color": "bg-orange-500"
    },

    
]
export default array